honestworkfromhomesuccess.com 2012-06-29

# Privacy Policy

PRIVACY POLICY

Honestworkfromhomesuccess.com, takes pride in creating richer, deeper interactive experiences that combines original, independent and user-generated content. 

Overall privacy statement

We take your privacy seriously. Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we want to help you understand the terms and conditions surrounding the collection and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses the types of information we gather, how we use it, and how to correct or change it. These privacy practices apply to the Web site that you were viewing when you clicked through to this policy, which is operated directly by us, by our partner, or by our affiliate. 

1\. What information does Honestworkfromhomesuccess.com collect? 

Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with the best and most useful content and services. Several of the services and features that we offer on our sites require you to provide us with information as a condition of usage. These include access to subscription-only areas, the ability to post opinions or other content, participation in contests and email newsletters and participation in message boards.   
We collect personally identifiable information, such as your name, email address, postal address, phone number, mobile number when you provide it to us. From time to time, we may also collect other sensitive information such as your job title, gender, username and password. 

2\. What is Honestworkfromhomesuccess.com practice regarding cookies? 

Your Internet browser has a feature called cookies, which stores small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to any of our sites. You do not need to have cookies turned on to visit most of our sites, although active participation in certain areas of our sites may require cookies. Cookies alone tell us nothing about who you are unless you specifically give us personally identifiable information, in which case we use the information to enhance your services in the ways described below. By adjusting your settings on your browser, you may elect not to allow cookies to be collected.   

[](http://www.honestworkfromhomesuccess.com/#)3\. How does Honestworkfromhomesuccess.com use the information? 

We use the information we gather for four general purposes: 

  1. To customize the advertising and the content you see; 
  2. To enhance the user experience in our network of sites. We use tracking information to determine how well each page performs overall based on aggregate user demographics and traffic patterns to those pages. This helps us continue to build a better service for you; 
  3. To fulfill your requests for certain products and services, such as sending out electronic newsletters and enabling you to participate in paid services, polls, contests, and message boards; 
  4. To send you information you agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to you. 

4\. How does Honestworkfromhomesuccess.com share the information? 

We never share your personal information EVER!

5\. What are my options? 

Users who would rather not provide any of the user data requested by our registration process do not need to register with us. You can still view much of the content and use many of the services offered by our sites without registering. 

6\. How can I review and update my personally identifiable information? 

You can review, correct, or change the information collected during registration for any of our sites. The instructions for doing this can be found in our member-services areas. Users may change information at any time and as often as necessary. Users who are experiencing problems with our services or who have questions about how our services work can contact us using e-mail addresses at the bottom of this page. 

Questions, Comments 

If you have any questions at all please don’t hesitate to contact us: 

webmaster@honestworkfromhomesuccess.com
